It is time for a Big Up Let Down.
But you know what?
There's no Big Up.
It's just two letdowns today.
I just wish that sometimes people would just keep it to themselves.
Billy Dee Williams and Gerard Carmichael in this case.
Bill Maher had Billy Dee, it was a Bill on Bill situation, on his podcast.
And when the subject of things that are unacceptable in film and stage today came up,
you know, like blackface, this is what Billy had to say.
They would never let you do that.
Why not?
Because you should do it.
If you're an actor, you should do anything you want to do.
Lando, what are you doing?
Stop.
That ain't it, Lando.
That ain't it.
I just feel like at this point, I just need Billy Dee to just keep it to himself.
Unless he's fighting Darth Vader or holding a cult 45, we don't need any insights.
We don't need it.
Then you had Gerard Carmichael.
Sometimes joke to him that, like, our relationship is like that of, like, a slave and the master
son who, like, teaches me how to reap my candlelight.
Is he joking?
Is he serious?
You know, jokes.
They're 60-40.
60% possible truth, 40% possible joke.
We never know what the real ratio is.
I don't want to know this is a joke he has with his white partner.
So the lesson we learned here is you can't unhear things once you hear them.
So now that I know that Billy Dee Williams is down with blackface and Gerard Carmichael
is down with slave play, you know too.